expertgps.com 2006-11-13

# ExpertGPS Privacy Policy

### ExpertGPS Privacy Policy

TopoGrafix takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. 

### What this Privacy Policy Covers

This Privacy Policy covers TopoGrafix's treatment of personally identifiable information that TopoGrafix collects when you are on the ExpertGPS site, and when you use the ExpertGPS software. This policy also covers TopoGrafix's treatment of any personally identifiable information that TopoGrafix's business partners share with TopoGrafix. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that TopoGrafix does not own or control, or to people that TopoGrafix does not employ or manage. 

TopoGrafix collects personally identifiable information when you visit expertgps.com or other TopoGrafix web pages, when you join our mailing list, and when you purchase our products. TopoGrafix may also receive personally identifiable information from our business partners. TopoGrafix also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, TopoGrafix cookie information and the page you requested. TopoGrafix uses information for three general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, and to contact you about specials and new products. 

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

TopoGrafix will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. TopoGrafix may send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when: We have your consent to share the information; We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested; We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of TopoGrafix to provide a product or service to you. (Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us.); or We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; 

### Cookies

TopoGrafix may set and access TopoGrafix cookies on your computer. TopoGrafix allows other companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to TopoGrafix's cookies. 

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

TopoGrafix may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages. 

TopoGrafix   
24 Kirkland Dr   
Stow, MA 01775
